welcome to JDK 9 my name is Alan Bateman
欢迎使用JDK 9，我叫Alan Bateman
I work in the Java platform group in
我在Java平台小组工作
Oracle a long time JDK contributor so
Oracle是JDK的长期贡献者
this session is prepared for JDK 9 um so
本次会议是为JDK 9 um准备的，因此
I'm going to start by just a quick poll
我将从快速民意调查开始
of the audience just to see how many
观众只是看有多少
people have downloaded and tries JDK 9
人们已经下载并尝试JDK 9
ok maybe about a third of the people so
好吧，大概有三分之一的人
for those that put up their hand how
对于那些举手的人
many people tried out their application
很多人尝试了他们的应用程序
or libraries and everything worked
或图书馆，一切正常
perfectly not too many hands how many
完全没有太多的手多少
people that put up their hand a few
举起手的人
minutes ago tried us and we're grumpy
分钟前尝试了我们，但我们脾气暴躁
for the rest of the day because
在一天的剩余时间内，因为
something broke same hands alright
东西摔坏了
you're in the right session this is the
你在正确的会议上，这是
list of features that are in JDK 9 this
JDK 9中的功能列表
is a screen capture of the all the list
是所有列表的屏幕截图
of jep's jdk enhance for proposals that
jep的jdk增强了建议
you'll find on the open JDK mjd canine
您会在开放的JDK mjd犬上找到
project page this big long list of
项目页面这个很大的清单
features this session is not about all
此会话的功能并非全部
of these features I will cover a couple
这些功能中，我将介绍几个
of the features but I'm not going to
的功能，但我不会
exhaustively go through all of these
详尽地经历所有这些
features instead I'm going to be mostly
功能，我将主要是
talking about the issues that you might
谈论您可能遇到的问题
run into and when you start preparing
遇到，当你开始准备
and thinking about moving to JDK 9
并考虑迁移到JDK 9
there's a lot of disruptive changes in
有很多破坏性的变化
JDK 9 my colleague Alex Buckley um wrote
JDK 9我的同事Alex Buckley um写道
the foreword for the book Java Java 9
Java Java 9本书的序言
modularity and in the foreword he
模块化，在序言中，他
likened the changes in JDK 9 to be a bit
将JDK 9中的更改比作一点
like the the tablecloth trick
像桌布的把戏
we've got cups and plates stacked on the
我们有杯子和盘子堆放在
table and you pull the tablecloth out
桌子，你把桌布拉出来
from without disrupting the plates and
从不破坏盘子和
cups but in Reverse
杯，但反向
there are some very deep changes that
有一些非常深刻的变化
have gone into JDK 9 so the big
已经进入JDK 9
challenge is to do the tablecloth trick
挑战是做桌布的把戏
in Reverse without disrupting the cups
在倒车时不打乱杯子
the plates and the heavy power tools
板和重型电动工具
that have accumulated on the table over
累积在桌子上
the last 20 years and there are a couple
最近20年，有几对
of little breakages and that's the top
很小的破损，那是最重要的
of things I want to talk about today so
我今天想谈的事情
this session is is actually the first of
本次会议实际上是
five sessions that we have in the
我们有五个会议
modularity track where since you track
模块化跟踪
within a track and talk about those
在轨道上谈论那些
later on at the end of this of this of
稍后在这个
the session so before we get into the
会议，所以在我们进入
into a few specifics I just want to talk
一些我只想谈的细节
about just the general compatibility
只是一般的兼容性
policies and if an application or a
政策以及应用程序或
library uses supported api's and works
库使用受支持的api和Works
on release in then it should work on
在发布时，它应该在
release in plus one even without
即使没有也可以释放一加
recompilation supported api's can be
重新编译支持的api可以是
removed but only with advance notice so
已删除，但仅在事先通知的情况下如此
let's see how we do on jdk 9 relative to
让我们看看我们如何在jdk 9上相对于
this policy the compatibility policy
此政策兼容性政策
that has existed for several years I'll
已经存在了几年，我会
start with the good news the classpath
从好消息开始
has not changed class loading has not
尚未更改类加载尚未
changed you are not forced to migrate
改变了你没有被迫迁移
your code to modules I've read a lot of
您的代码到模块我已经读了很多
articles and postings by people that
人们的文章和帖子
think that you're forced to move your
认为你被迫搬家
and migrate all your existing code
并迁移所有现有代码
modules in order to move to JDK 9 they
为了转移到JDK 9
are confused ignore them you may have
感到困惑，请忽略它们
heard of Sun Muskaan safe you may not
听说太阳穆斯卡安很安全，你可能不知道
use it directly in your code but the
直接在您的代码中使用它，但是
chances are some library that you use
可能是您使用的一些库
that you have on the class path today is
你今天在上课的路上是
using Sun Muskaan safe it works as
使用Sun Muskaan safe可以像
before most existing code actually just
在大多数现有代码之前
works as before
像以前一样工作
as we go through this presentation
当我们浏览此演示文稿时
you'll actually see there really isn't a
您实际上会发现那里确实没有
huge amount of code changes involved
涉及大量的代码更改
final point on on the good news is all
关于好消息的最后一点就是全部
the mainstream IDs maven and all of its
主流ID专家及其所有
plugins are most of its plugins they
插件是其大多数插件
already have support for JDK 9 their JDK
已经对其JDK 9提供了支持
9 ready
9准备好了
and quotes um by last week when we
并在上周引用um时
eventually shipped JDK 9 so that's the
最终发布了JDK 9，因此
good news
好消息
the not-so-good news which is a nicer
不太好消息，这是一个更好的消息
way of saying the bad news you will most
你最会说坏消息的方式
likely need to upgrade many of the
可能需要升级许多
libraries and the tools that you use if
库和您使用的工具
you are directly using some of the
您正在直接使用一些
libraries that are shared some of the
共享一些
API is that are where there's a there's
API就是在那里
a version for EE and a version for Java
EE版本和Java版本
C but they're the same library but there
C，但它们是同一个库，但是在那里
aren't they're not exactly in sync if
他们不是完全不同步，如果
you're using those directly you may have
你直接使用那些你可能有
to do some adjustments to your build or
对您的构建进行一些调整，或者
your class path I'll talk about that in
你的上课道路我会在
in a few minutes
在几分钟内
a number of supported api's have been
许多受支持的API
removed
已移除
they were deprecated sometime ago and
他们在某个时候过时了，
they were removed we're talking about
他们被删除，我们正在谈论
six methods from the Java C API which is
Java C API的六个方法是
not a lot we remove those right in the
我们没有删除很多权利
first build of JDK 9 several years ago
几年前的第一个JDK 9构建
nobody has complained so I'm not gonna
没有人抱怨，所以我不会
bother covering them in this
麻烦他们覆盖这个
presentation because obviously know
介绍，因为显然知道
people don't really care about them
人们真的不在乎他们
there's a number of non API features and
有很多非API功能，
some some tools have been removed and
一些工具已被删除，
people have not complained about them so
人们没有抱怨他们，所以
I'm not going to cover them either
我也不会掩盖
because they're not significant things
因为它们不是重要的东西
you will see some warnings possibly and
您可能会看到一些警告，
printed by the runtime because of things
由于某些原因由运行时打印
that libraries are using are doing I'll
图书馆正在使用的我会
talk about that in in in in this
在此谈论
presentation so dive into a couple of
演示文稿，因此请深入了解
items first is the modules that are
项目首先是
shared between Java SE and Java EE so
Java SE和Java EE之间共享，因此
one of the things about the Java Sea and
关于JAVA海和
the JDK is is that it it's assimilated
JDK是它被同化了
many technologies and over the last
在过去的许多技术中
couple of years and so a bit like the
几年，所以有点像
board some people have likened it to the
登上一些人把它比作
Borg and many years ago where it
博格和很多年前
assimilated many different cultures and
吸收了许多不同的文化
technologies and while they didn't show
技术，虽然它们没有显示
it in any episode of Star Trek I'm
在《星际迷航》的任何一集中
pretty sure that the Borg actually had
很确定博格实际上有
regrets from time to time the JDK did
JDK有时会后悔
too
太
this is the Java C module graph if
这是Java C模块图，如果
you've been to Java one before you've
您在去过Java之前就去过
seen any our presentations over the
看过我们的任何演讲
years on modules you will have seen that
年的模块，您将看到
we worked through over the years from a
我们从
spaghetti diagram to a relatively clean
意大利面图要比较干净
directed graph that you see here there
你在这里看到的有向图
are many modules in this that originally
本来有很多模块
were standalone technologies or lies the
是独立技术还是谎言
the the font is small in there but if I
那里的字体很小，但是如果我
were to look I'll easily spot things
看起来我会很容易发现
like Java management that includes GM X
例如包含GM X的Java管理
that was a standalone technology at one
那是一项独立的技术
point I see Java naming that was jndi
我看到的Java命名是jndi
and a standalone technology at one point
一站式的技术
what we have open the right side of the
我们打开了右侧的
the graph is a bunch of modules that
该图是一堆模块，
overlap with Java EE and these have not
与Java EE重叠，并且没有
been completely subsumed so I'm going to
被完全包含，所以我要
I'm going to start putting a little
我要开始放一点
label I'm gonna use a black star to
标签，我要用黑星来
label these these api's are never fully
标记这些API永远不会完全
subsumed in into Java C and you will
包含在Java C中，您将
actually see that these become
实际上看到这些变成
problematic api's when you're moving
有问题的api，当您移动时
from eight to nine because of because of
从八到九，因为
this overlap so I've put a black star
这个重叠，所以我放了一颗黑星
over four api's that are two of them are
超过四个API，其中两个是
really trouble to them are less trouble
对他们来说真正的麻烦少了
but they're they have equal problems two
但是他们有两个同样的问题
of these two of these modules bring
这些模块中的两个带来了
along a body that you have activation
沿着被激活的身体
module there's no business being in Java
模块在Java中没有业务
C but it has ends up being a standalone
C，但最终却是独立的
technology outside of the JDK and being
JDK之外的技术
in the JDK at the same time like these
像这样同时在JDK中
four other modules very very problematic
其他四个模块非常有问题
I'm also going to put a black star
我也要放一个黑星
against the core of a module and the
针对模块的核心和
reason for that is is CORBA has been a
原因是CORBA一直是
whipping boy for modules for the last
鞭打男孩最后的模块
number of years but the real reason of
年数，但真正的原因
course is that korba is actually
当然，科尔巴实际上是
dependent on one of these problematic
取决于这些问题之一
modules it's dependent on the
模块取决于
transaction API where Java C defines a
交易API，其中Java C定义了
subset of this Java EE defines a
此Java EE的子集定义了一个
that the full API and there's a really
完整的API，还有一个
really problematic area and when you
真正有问题的区域以及当您
move to modules so this business of
转移到模块，这样的业务
being inside the JDK and outside of the
在JDK内部和外部
JDK and at the same time is essentially
JDK和本质上同时
technical debt for the JDK and when you
JDK的技术债务以及您何时
move any big codebase to modules you
将任何大型代码库移至您的模块
probably run into some technical death
可能会遇到技术故障
this possibly is unique to to the JDK
这可能是JDK特有的
and but it's still technical data that
但这仍然是技术数据
we have to somehow figure out you can't
我们必须以某种方式弄清楚你不能
override modules in the JDK by putting
通过放置JDK中的模块
jar files on the classpath you can't
您无法在类路径上的jar文件
jar files in the indoor standards
室内标准中的jar文件
override mechanism because that
覆盖机制，因为
mechanism has gone the only way to
机制已经成为唯一的途径
override modules in the JDK with newer
使用更新的版本覆盖JDK中的模块
versions is through the upgrade module
版本是通过升级模块
mechanism which is a new mechanism in
机制，这是一种新的机制
nine and only if the modules are aligned
九个且仅当模块对齐时
with the modules that you have SE
与您拥有SE的模块
defines and this is where we have the
定义，这就是我们拥有的
problems with each one of these modules
这些模块中的每一个都有问题
so this is this is a topic that has been
所以这是一个已经存在的话题
we have been mulling over for a long
我们已经考虑了很长时间
time and fundamentally what's happening
时间和根本上发生了什么
is is the JDK was the delivery vehicle
是JDK是交付工具
from from any of these api's its 2017
从任何这些api的2017年
now there's no reason for it to be the
现在没有理由成为
delivery vehicle for these api's each of
这些api的传送工具
these api's has a standalone version and
这些api具有独立版本，
there's no reason why the jdk needs to
没有理由为什么jdk需要
to really have them so the proposal a
真正拥有他们，所以提案
long time back in java c which was
很久以前在java c中
eventually accepted was the deprecated
最终被弃用了
each of these modules and here are the
每个模块，这是
six here's the names of these modules
六个是这些模块的名称
Java Korba which is the core of API and
Java Korba是API的核心，
an RMI ILP the driver transaction API
RMI ILP驱动程序事务API
which is the biggest troublemaker in in
这是最大的麻烦制造者
the lot here in that because Java C
这是因为Java C
defines a small subset of the
定义了
transaction API to have activation
交易API需要激活
because it has no business being in here
因为这里没有生意
Javik smell bind which is the xml
Javik气味绑定，这是XML
binding api this may be something that
绑定api这可能是
you use directly or maybe some library
您直接使用或使用某些库
the use it's probably the most popular
使用可能是最受欢迎的
one on this list here java xml WS which
此列表上的一个Java xml WS其中
is the web services and so put
是网络服务，因此
attachments all of that stuff 2017
附件所有这些东西2017
kind of legacy now Jeff XML WS
现在的旧版Jeff XML WS
annotation which is actually a subset of
批注实际上是
these of this of this API called the
这个API的这些称为
common annotations a Java EE provides a
Java EE提供的常见注释
subset of that API was defined for Java
该API的子集是为Java定义的
C to support web services and it ended
C支持Web服务，它结束了
up in Java C and one thing about these
Java C和有关这些的一件事
modules is as they are deprecated for
模块是因为不推荐使用
removal this is a new form of
去除这是一种新的形式
deprecation and that was introduced in
弃用，并在
Java C 9 when a module or some other
Java C 9当一个模块或其他模块
programming element may be a class or
编程元素可以是类或
may be a particular method is marked
可能是被标记的特定方法
deprecated for removal it's providing a
不建议移除，它提供了
clear intent that it will be removed at
明确的意图是将其删除
some point the compiler and the Java
有一点编译器和Java
language know about methods that and
语言了解有关方法和
programming elements that are actually
实际上是编程元素
deprecated for removal it knows to give
不赞成删除，它知道要给
you the right warning for example so if
您正确的警告，例如，如果
you're using any of these you don't need
您正在使用不需要的任何这些
to panic and we get into some of these
恐慌，我们进入其中一些
things in a few minutes but let me just
几分钟之内的事情，但让我
show you what one other thing that has
告诉你还有另一件事
happened in 9 so they're deprecated for
发生在9，所以他们不赞成
removal but we have also made one other
搬迁，但我们也做了一个
adjustment which will smooth the path to
调整，这将为
eventually removing these from Java Sea
最终将它们从JAVA海中删除
and the JDK and that change is that we
和JDK的区别在于，我们
will not resolve these modules by
不会通过解析这些模块
default now you haven't gone to there
现在默认，您还没有去过那里
are some modules talks yet so you don't
有一些模块讨论，所以你不
know what resolution and-and-and-and-and
知道什么分辨率，又又又又又
resolving modules means but don't worry
解决模块意味着但不用担心
about that what it means is is that is
关于这意味着什么是
is essentially it's if you're running
本质上是如果您正在跑步
code on the class path it will be as if
类路径上的代码就像
these modules don't exist it will be as
这些模块不存在，它将是
if the types in these modules do not
如果这些模块中的类型不
exist and let me show you an example
存在，让我给你看一个例子
which acts be just to reinforce what
只是为了加强什么
this means so here's a little code
这意味着这是一些代码
fragment using using using M Jax Jax B's
使用M Jax Jax B的片段
API I'm calling a static method on on
API，我正在调用静态方法
mjx XML bind and
mjx XML绑定和
Jax be context this a static method to
Jax被上下文这是一个静态方法
to get it a Jax be context don't worry
让它成为上下文的Jax不必担心
if you've never used Jax be you can just
如果您从未使用过Jax，可以
ignore this the important point is the
忽略这一点，重要的是
next what I want to show you what
接下来我想告诉你什么
happens if you attempt to compile this
如果您尝试编译此发生
code you get a compiler error it will
代码，您会收到一个编译器错误，它将
not compile I'll read out the error
无法编译，我会读出错误
package javax.swing I'll bind is not
我绑定的包javax.swing不是
visible packaged Avex ml bind is
可见包装的Avex ml绑定是
declared in module java xml bind which
在模块java xml中声明的bind
is not in the module graph when I said
当我说时不在模块图中
that the module is not resolved it's not
该模块没有解决，不是
in this module graph that the the
在此模块图中，
runtime has hurt so the compiler has a
运行时受到伤害，因此编译器有一个
none runtime has when it actually starts
实际启动时没有运行时
up and when you're compiling code a
以及在编译代码时
running code on the class path so if you
在类路径上运行代码，如果
get this error when you're compiling
编译时出现此错误
what happens if I've already got some
如果我已经有一些会发生什么
code that's previously compiled to use
先前编译使用的代码
these api's and I try to run it shock
这些api，我尝试让它震惊
horror I get in no class dev founder
可怕的是我没有班级开发者
it's as if I'm missing a jar file on my
好像我缺少我的jar文件
class path which is exactly what what's
类路径到底是什么
what's going on so this is a new thing
这是怎么回事，所以这是新事物
to the JDK and we have never removed
到JDK，我们从未删除
modules before and this is just the
模块之前，这只是
first step and I want to talk about some
第一步，我想谈一些
of the migration options are that are
的迁移选项是
around this this is most certainly a
围绕这个，这肯定是一个
disruptive change but only for those
颠覆性变革，但仅针对那些
that are directly using and indirectly
直接使用和间接使用的
using the API is in these modules
这些模块中使用了API
there's a number of migration options
有很多迁移选项
and we've written these up in the jdk
我们已经在jdk中编写了这些
migration guide we have a new
迁移指南，我们有一个新的
command-line option add modules where
命令行选项添加模块，其中
you give it a set of modules that will
您给它提供一组模块
be additionally resolved at startup and
在启动时另外解决
this is useful as a short term solution
这可用作短期解决方案
to get existing code that's using these
获得使用这些的现有代码
api's to compile and run it runs exactly
编译并运行它的api
like jdk age all the way back to 6 did
就像jdk的年龄一直回到6岁
in the case of this module so this keeps
在这个模块的情况下，这样保持
existing code code working
现有代码工作正常
obvious with the inconvenience of adding
添加带来的不便
a command-line option each of these
每个选项都有一个命令行选项
api's except for carbon has its own
api的碳元素除外
standalone version it has its own jsr
独立版本，它有自己的jsr
that maintains it in the JCP each the
每个JCP都维护它
artifacts for each one of these modules
这些模块中的每个模块的工件
are published our jar files I should say
已经发布了我们的jar文件，我应该说
are published in maven central so
在maven Central中发布，因此
there's alternative ways of getting
还有其他获取方式
these libraries when you use them and
这些库，当您使用它们时
you can deploy those on the class path
您可以将它们部署在类路径上
or you can deploy them on the upgrade
或者您可以在升级时部署它们
module path so they're deployed as
模块路径，以便将它们部署为
modules now they're not all quite there
模块现在还不全在
yet as as modules but the a colleague of
作为模块，但作为一个同事
mine is sorting it out with the owners
我正在和业主一起整理
of all of the these components to make
所有这些组成部分中
sure that eventually they can all be
确保最终他们都可以成为
deployed as modules as well so that's
也部署为模块，所以
one big important change in nosotros
鼻腔治疗器的一项重要重要改变
disruptive change and I want to move on
颠覆性的变化，我想继续
and talk about strong encapsulation
谈论强封装
which for the JDK is all about
对于JDK而言，
encapsulating the JDK internals so that
封装JDK内部，以便
code outside of the modules these
这些模块之外的代码
modules will not be able to get at the
模块将无法到达
the classes that are not part of the API
不属于API的类
and are and also so they cannot get at
而且也是，所以他们无法到达
the non-public members of classes that
班级的非公开成员
are in the API so this is a this is a
在API中，所以这是一个
big deal I've got a start by going back
大不了的，我先回去
20 years this dusty duct slide dusty
这个尘土飞扬的管道滑道20年尘土飞扬
Docs page is from 1996 and I will try to
文档页面是从1996年开始的，我将尝试
read it
阅读
miss anyone down the back has brought
想念背后的任何人带来了
binoculars and can read it for me the
双筒望远镜，可以为我阅读
Java dot star package makes makeup the
Java点星包使化妆
official supported public Java interface
官方支持的公共Java接口
the Sun dot star packages are not part
Sun dot star软件包不包含在内
of the supported public Java interface
支持的公共Java接口
this says this is what the documentation
这说这是文档
said 21 years ago but no one ever reads
说21年前，但没人读过
these documentation now things dialed up
这些文档现在事情已经过去了
in JDK 6 when Java C acquired a simple
在JDK 6中，当Java C获得一个简单的
database the symbol database was enough
符号数据库就足够了
for Java C to be able to print warnings
Java C能够打印警告
our errors when compiling code that was
我们在编译代码时的错误是
making use of of Sun dot star api's or
利用Sun dot star API或
other internal api's this acts as a
其他内部api的作用是
deterrent so I'm going to pick a little
威慑力，所以我要挑一些
example here of code that has a static
具有静态代码的示例
reference to Sun security x.509 X 500
参考Sun Security x.509 X 500
name and we'll see what happens when you
名称，我们将看到您发生什么情况
try to compile this with JDK 6 or 7 or 8
尝试使用JDK 6或7或8进行编译
you get a compiler warning
您收到编译器警告
what is the warning warning X 500 name
警告X 500名称是什么
is internal proprietary API and may be
是内部专有API，可能是
removed any future release we all ignore
删除了所有我们都忽略的未来版本
pilot warnings I'm sure here so with
飞行员警告，我肯定在这里
ignore the documentation we've ignored
忽略我们忽略的文档
the the compiler warning now let's move
编译器警告现在开始
to JDK 9 where things dial up another
到JDK 9，那里的东西又拨号了
little bit with JDK 9 if you attempt a
如果您尝试使用JDK 9，
compiled code with a direct reference to
直接参考的已编译代码
internal API the compilation will fail
内部API编译将失败
end of story
故事结局
I'll read out the air
我会宣扬空气
package son security x.509 is not
包子安全x.509不是
visible packages son security x.509 is
可见的安全性x.509软件包是
declared module base which is not which
声明的模块库不是
does not export it to the unnamed module
不会将其导出到未命名的模块
now we don't know what the unnamed
现在我们不知道未命名的是什么
module is here because we haven't been
模块在这里，因为我们还没有去过
to the other and the other sessions but
参加其他会议，但
just assume it's a class path for this
只是假设这是一个类路径
presentation summary is compiling
演示文稿摘要正在编译
against internal api's and will now lead
针对内部api，现在将导致
to compilation errors in jdk 9 so what
在jdk 9中编译错误
about one time so this is more
大约一次，所以更多
complicated at run time oh I forgot one
在运行时很复杂哦，我忘了一个
order thing J tips very useful tool when
订购东西J技巧时非常有用的工具
preparing for JDK 9 is to run the Jade
为JDK 9做准备就是运行Jade
EPS tool and the Jade EPS tool is in JDK
JDK中包含EPS工具和Jade EPS工具
8 and allows you to do a static analysis
8，并允许您进行静态分析
of your code or compile code to see if
代码或编译代码以查看是否
it has any references to internal api's
它具有对内部api的任何引用
it's actually a bit of a Swiss Army
实际上是一支瑞士军队
knife you can actually get it to be able
刀，你实际上可以得到它能够
to look at it and analyze all your
看看并分析所有
dependencies it's very very useful tool
依赖关系，这是非常非常有用的工具
and quick poll actually how many people
快速调查实际上有多少人
here have tried J tips ok that's better
这里尝试过J技巧好吧
than last year which is good so for
比去年好
those that are taking photos Jade EPS is
那些拍照片的翡翠EPS是
jde PSM so can we often get asked in
jde PSM，所以我们经常会被问到吗
presentations just to spell that out so
演示只是为了说明这一点
I'm going to run Jade apps just on that
我将仅以此运行Jade应用
code example I had in the previous slide
我上一张幻灯片中的代码示例
and I'm using J tips - JDK internals
我正在使用J技巧-JDK内部
giving it the class I can give it jar
给它上课我可以给它加罐子
files you can give a class path that's
您可以提供一个类路径的文件
actually very quite flexible what its
实际上非常灵活
input would be and it's putting out a
输入将是，它正在推出
message to say that my code has a
消息说我的代码有一个
dependency on Sun security x.509 X 500
对Sun Security x.509 X 500的依赖
name and it Flags it as an internal API
名称并将其标记为内部API
Jade EPS has been improved quite a bit
翡翠EPS有了很大的提高
in JDK 9 so if you've tried an 8 you'll
在JDK 9中，如果您尝试过8，
actually see some improvements in 9 but
实际上在9中看到了一些改进，但是
one of the nice things it has is it has
它具有的优点之一就是它具有
a little table of internal API is vs.
一张内部API的小表格是vs。
supported api's so for cases where into
支持的api，因此适用于
any supported API is have been
任何受支持的API
introduced and it sees a reference to
介绍，它看到了对
the old internal API it'll actually give
实际上会提供的旧内部API
you a hint in this case there's a
你在这种情况下有一个提示
there's an X 500 principal class that
有一个X 500的主要班级
was added and 1/4 which is a much better
加了1/4更好了
way of
的方法
dealing with x500 names now I want to go
现在我要处理x500名称
back to run time again and talk about
回到运行时间再谈
the complexity but with the run time the
复杂性，但随着运行时间
ultimate goal is to encapsulate all
最终目标是封装所有
internal api's at one time as well we're
一次也有内部api
not there yet in jdk 9 we attempted to
在jdk 9中我们还没有尝试
go there in j2k 9 and in fact for over a
在j2k 9中去那里，实际上超过
year we had early access bills that
一年，我们有早期访问账单
strongly encapsulated all of the
强烈封装了所有
internals at runtime
运行时内部
but a lot of code broke a lot of code is
但是很多代码破坏了很多代码是
making use of internal ap is a lot of
利用内部ap的很多
code is hacking into non-public members
代码侵入非公共成员
of classes in Java lang
Java lang中的类的集合
so what is the story for JDK 9 and
那么JDK 9和
runtime now this is a summary of where
现在是运行时的摘要
things are with JDK 9 now I'll read this
现在，JDK 9可以解决问题
out all packages that existed in JDK 8
排除JDK 8中存在的所有软件包
are open to code on the class path this
在类路径上对此代码开放
allows existing hacks to work as before
允许现有的黑客像以前一样工作
now when I say existing hacks work
现在当我说现有的黑客工作
before you will of course have
在您当然拥有之前
refactoring of internal classes and
内部类的重构和
things that break a lot of these hacks
破坏了很多黑客的东西
anyways and that's just that's just part
无论如何，那只是一部分
of our of life a first and this is this
是我们生命中的第一，这是
an important point is the first use of
重要的一点是第一次使用
core reflection that makes use that
利用这一点的核心思考
hacks into JDK internals are does what
入侵JDK内部是做什么的
we call an illegal reflective access and
我们称其为非法反射访问，
I explain that in a few minutes will
我解释一下，几分钟后
emit a warning to standard error that's
向标准错误发出警告
a non suppressible warning and so this
不可抑制的警告，所以这
is the first time that we've imaged
是我们第一次成像
warnings at runtime the warning which
运行时的警告
I'll show in the next slide is there to
我将在下一张幻灯片中显示
create awareness that there is code that
使人们意识到有代码
will break when the internals are
当内部结构破损时
completely encapsulated
完全封装
the warning attempts to identify what
警告试图识别出什么
the offending code is and tells you what
令人讨厌的代码是告诉你什么
it's actually trying to access them
它实际上是试图访问它们
there is a command-line option - -
有一个命令行选项--
illegal access that allows you to debug
允许您调试的非法访问
further so future debug one of these you
更进一步，以便将来调试其中一个
can get in you can get
可以进入你可以得到
additional warnings you can get stacked
您可能会堆积的其他警告
races you can even have it deny access
种族，您甚至可以拒绝访问
to internals which allows you to try out
内部结构，让您可以尝试
what future behavior will be when the
当
the GDK fully encapsulates its internals
GDK完全封装了其内部
so I'm going to use an example I'm using
所以我要用一个例子
the example of the Jason ripple and by
杰森波纹的例子
the way I'm not picking on Jason I'm
我没有选择杰森的方式
just using it as an example there are
仅以它为例
many examples I could have chosen last
最后我可以选择很多例子
year and the previous year I used
我用的一年和前一年
examples with Gradle and and GlassFish I
Gradle和GlassFish I的示例
decided to give them a break this year
决定今年休息一下
so let's look what the warning is so I'm
让我们看看警告是什么
this is an executable jar of the Java
这是Java的可执行jar
dash jar I get a warning and the legal
dash jar我收到警告和法律
reflective access operation has occurred
发生反射访问操作
illegal reflective access by and it
和它的非法反射访问
gives me the type name it gives me the
给我类型名称，给我
the codebase in this case it's the it's
在这种情况下的代码库是
the jar file with the Jason ripple and
带有Jason波纹的jar文件和
it's trying to access some a member of
它正在尝试访问某些成员
Sun and IO CH and this is a selectable
Sun和IO CH，这是可选的
channel implementation internals is
渠道实施内部是
trying to access this the access will
尝试访问此访问
succeed but you get this warning and it
成功，但是您收到此警告，并且它
gives a suggestion about submitting a
提出有关提交
bug and giving you also hint as to what
错误，还提示您什么
command-line option you can actually use
您可以实际使用的命令行选项
to get further warnings if you want to
以获得进一步的警告，如果你想
investigators so this is a new thing and
调查人员，所以这是新事物，
warnings at one time now there's lots of
一次警告现在有很多
other changes in gene JDK 9 that I want
我想要的基因JDK 9中的其他变化
to talk about him the new version string
谈谈他的新版本字符串
scheme chip 223 and you may have heard
方案芯片223，您可能听说过
of this this is actually quite of a
这实际上是相当
disruptive change I'm not going to spend
我不会花费的颠覆性变革
time going through it the chip has all
时间经过它，芯片拥有了所有
of the motivations for why the old
为什么旧的动机
confusing numbering scheme is being
令人困惑的编号方案
replaced with a newer numbering scheme
替换为新的编号方案
which is a lot simpler and I hope people
这要简单得多，我希望人们
will figure it out a lot simpler so
会弄清楚很多，所以
here's an example ours are just a table
这是一个例子，我们只是一张桌子
showing JDK 8 vs j TK 9
显示JDK 8 vs j TK 9
these are the four five assistant
这些是四个五个助手
properties that and reveal the version
并显示版本的属性
and Java version by is the assistant
Java版本by是助手
property that many libraries and examine
许多图书馆和检查的财产
to see what they are running on so it's
看看他们在做什么，所以
nice and simple and after 20 years we've
漂亮而简单，经过20年的发展
essentially dropped the leading one but
本质上放弃了领先者，但
that is an extremely disruptive change I
这是一个极具破坏性的变化
could do an entire session on code
可以在代码上进行整个会话
examples showing bad code parsing the
显示错误代码的示例
Java version we've seen code that thinks
Java版本，我们已经看到了认为
it's on JD k 1j tk1 one when it's
它在JD k 1j tk1上时
running on nine we've seen we've seen
跑了九个我们已经看到我们已经看到
code that actually tries to execute and
实际尝试执行的代码
and load libraries that had never that
并加载从未有过的库
it hasn't run in more than ten years
它已经运行了十多年
we've seen exceptions we've seen errors
我们看到了异常我们看到了错误
all sorts of crazy things there's enough
各种疯狂的事情就足够了
material there for an entire session at
整个会议的材料
the San Francisco comedy club so many
旧金山喜剧俱乐部很多
libraries have already been working with
图书馆已经与
us over the last few years and have have
我们在过去的几年中有
affixed the parsing to be able to deal
附加了解析后即可处理
with nine and there but there's probably
有九个，但那里可能
other code out there if you maintain any
如果您维护任何其他代码
code that is parsing Java version now is
现在解析Java版本的代码是
a good time to audit to see and whether
审核的好时机，看看是否
it'll actually have issues and moving
实际上会有问题和动
from eight to nine so a couple of things
从八点到九点
features that are on nine that are
在九个功能上
actually avoid having to parse the Java
实际上避免了解析Java
version is with a new runtime version
版本带有新的运行时版本
API
API
so finally you actually have a
所以最后你实际上有一个
programmatic way to get the version now
现在以编程方式获取版本
this week you'll hear a lot about moving
这周你会听到很多关于搬家的信息
to faster releases and maybe changing
到更快的版本，也许会改变
the version scheme again so maybe this
版本方案再次，所以也许这
API will have to be revisited but the
必须重新审查API，但
point is it's much nicer to be able to
关键是能够更好
use a API to get this information rather
使用API​​而不是获取此信息
than doing your own parsing we also have
而不是自己解析，
multi release jars and which is is
多释放罐，这是
something I'm going to talk about later
我稍后要谈论的东西
in the present presentation the new
在本演示文稿中，新
binary structure are for the JRE in the
二进制结构是针对JRE中的
JDK yep 220 and this is this is all
JDK是220，这就是全部
about
关于
dealing with the moving to a modular
转向模块化
platform because one of the implications
平台，因为其中的意义之一
of a modular platform is it completely
模块化平台是否完全
blurs the historical distinction between
模糊了两者之间的历史区别
the JRE and the JDK and this is a
JRE和JDK，这是一个
disruptive change and one of the reasons
破坏性变化和原因之一
we got this in early in JDK now in fact
实际上，我们早在JDK上就已经有了
we got it in late 2014 so that the tools
我们在2014年末获得了该工具
and the compilers and the ideas and
以及编译器和想法以及
those that are actually dependent on the
那些实际上依赖于
layout on the file system could be a
文件系统上的布局可能是
just in advance to deal with this change
只是提前应对这种变化
so what does this mean it means that the
所以这意味着什么
sorry I'll show you the legacy structure
抱歉，我会向您展示旧结构
first just so you have some idea where
首先只是为了让您有所了解
we're actually moving from the JDK view
我们实际上是从JDK观点出发
download eight seven six all the way
一路下载八七六
back to 1.2 where this structure was
回到1.2的结构
introduced you have a JRE directory
介绍您有一个JRE目录
within the JDK download that has the
在JDK下载中
runtime there's a Lib directory where
运行时有一个Lib目录
you have Archie jar you've probably
你可能有Archie jar
heard of RT jar there's a Lib directory
听说RT jar有一个Lib目录
at the top level Lib directory where
在顶层Lib目录中
you'll find additional jar files tools
您会发现其他jar文件工具
that jar is probably the the best-known
那个罐子可能是最有名的
there are two bin directories one at the
有两个bin目录，其中一个位于
top level one under Jerry
杰里（Jerry）的最高一级
they have copies of the same tool this
他们有相同工具的副本
is an embarrassing accident the way this
这是一个令人尴尬的事故
is layout and came came about the Lib
是布局，来了关于库
directory is is a hodgepodge of things
目录是事物的大杂烩
and it has some files in there that are
它里面有一些文件
intended to be edited they've provide
打算对其提供的内容进行编辑
configurations like the the management
像管理这样的配置
configuration file our security policy
配置文件我们的安全策略
file they're intended to be edited
他们打算被编辑的文件
there's a whole bunch of other files in
里面有一堆其他文件
there you touch them the JDK is hosed
在那里，您可以触摸它们
you're not supposed to edit them so
你不应该编辑它们
there was always confusion as to what
人们总是对什么感到困惑
you should change and watch what what
你应该改变并注意什么
not to change JDK 9 runtime emission
不更改JDK 9运行时发射
format runtime which is much simpler one
格式化运行时，这要简单得多
level one bin directory with the tools
使用工具将一级bin目录
the Java launcher Java C and so on it
Java启动器Java C等
comes directly with the user editable
直接与用户一起编辑
configuration file if it's if it's
配置文件（如果有）
tended to be edited it's in that
倾向于被编辑
directory if it's not intended to be
目录，如果不打算
edited it's not there so what this means
编辑它不在那里，这意味着什么
is the JRE directory is gone RTG are
是JRE目录消失了RTG是
sorry Archie jars
对不起，阿奇罐子
to that jar is gone so this is a big
那个罐子不见了，所以这是一个很大的
change you know I assume most people
改变，你知道我认为大多数人
here won't have code that's too
这里不会有太多的代码
dependent on this what many of the tools
依赖于此，许多工具
that you use probably do is that's one
您使用的可能就是那个
of the reasons for having to upgrade
必须升级的原因
your tools now if you go to the module
现在，如果您进入模块，则可以使用您的工具
sessions you'll hear a little bit about
会话，您会听到一些有关
the j-link tool and creating your own
j-link工具并创建自己的工具
runtime image and by linking just the
运行时映像并仅链接
modules that you want into create your
您想要创建的模块
own runtime when you use j-link then you
使用j-link时拥有自己的运行时
may start becoming familiar with with
可能开始熟悉
with this layout there's many other
通过这种布局，还有许多其他功能
changes I talked I said earlier on that
我刚才说过的变化
the classpath hasn't change class
类路径没有改变类
loading hasn't changed but there are
加载没有改变，但是有
actually a couple of changes in this
实际上在这方面有一些变化
area the application class loader
应用程序类加载器区域
is no longer an instance of URL class
不再是URL类的实例
loader
装载机
it was never documented as such what we
从来没有这样记录过我们
found many libraries out there that
发现那里有很多图书馆
assume this and really want it to be in
假设这并真的希望它存在
a URL class loader all of the core
URL类加载器的所有核心
modules that you that used to be used
您曾经使用过的模块
where their classes used to be an RTG
他们的班级曾经是RTG
are there they're all in modules now
现在它们都在模块中了吗
there is no need for a boo class path so
不需要布尔类路径，因此
there's some changes there these are
有一些变化，这些是
things you probably won't won't run into
你可能不会碰到的东西
too much but if you've got your own
太多了，但是如果你有自己的
custom class loader and it's a 10 it's
自定义类加载器，它是10
it's the parent didn't know then
那是父母不知道的
suddenly the set of types that are
突然的是
visible to it ar-ar-ar-ar reduce so
对它可见ar-ar-ar-ar减少所以
things two things to be aware of nothing
事情两件事，什么都不知道
to do with modules but there was a lot
与模块有关，但有很多
of security defense-in-depth work done
安全深度防御工作完成
in jdk 9 to move a lot of the non-core
在jdk 9中移动了很多非核心
libraries and modules away from the
库和模块远离
bootloader where they've where they've
引导加载程序所在位置所在位置
all permissions they've been moved to
他们已移至的所有权限
the platform class loader or the
平台类加载器或
extension class loader as it used to be
扩展类加载器，因为它曾经是
so this is another thing that
所以这是另一回事
co-creating and custom class loaders may
共同创建和自定义类加载器可以
actually and have may actually observe
实际上并且可能实际上观察到了
one of the brave things that was done in
做的勇敢的事情之一
JDK 9 is to move through the Unicode
JDK 9将遍历Unicode
cldr
cldr
locale data by default now this is a
默认情况下，语言环境数据是
really subtle change but it's a really
非常微妙的变化，但这是一个非常
really good change so this is something
真的是很好的改变，这就是
that has been preparation for many years
已经准备好多年了
and for for almost 20 years the GDK
以及将近20年的GDK
maintained its own locale data we call
维护我们自己的语言环境数据
it and we now call it the the legacy JRE
它，我们现在将其称为旧版JRE
locale data jdk age was updated to ship
语言环境数据jdk年龄已更新为可发货
with two sets of locale data and there's
有两套语言环境数据，
a system property that you can flip flip
您可以翻转的系统属性
between the two of them it did not
他们两个之间没有
change the default JDK 9 switches the
更改默认的JDK 9开关
default
默认
and this is this is if you've got
这就是如果你有
applications that are deployed and I
部署的应用程序和我
guess I've reading something there
猜猜我在那儿读东西
recently someone someone was running
最近有人在跑步
into some strange formatting of dates
变成一些奇怪的日期格式
issue and I think it was Australian
问题，我认为是澳大利亚人
English and it was a subtle difference
英语，这是一个微妙的区别
between the standardised cldr and the
在标准化的cldr和
old Gerry locale data
旧的格里语言环境数据
the format was slightly different and it
格式略有不同，
had been updated a couple years ago and
已经在几年前更新了
cldr
cldr
so these are little subtle things to be
所以这些都是微妙的事情
aware of but what you can do with JDK is
知道，但是您可以使用JDK做的是
you can configure to you cldr and you
您可以为您配置cldr，然后您
can actually observe then in the
可以实际观察到
different locales that you support to
您支持的不同语言环境
see whether you've only any any
看你是否只有一个
differences JDK 9 also took the brave
JDK 9的差异也很勇敢
step of switching the the the default
切换默认值的步骤
garbage collector to g1 and which
垃圾收集器到g1，哪个
potentially will change the performance
可能会改变性能
characteristics of of some applications
一些应用程序的特征
I'm not going into all of these in
我不会在所有这些
detail now just really making aware of
现在，细节才真正使人意识到
things to think about when you're moving
移动时要考虑的事情
to gjd canine now what i want to move on
现在我要继续前进到gjd犬
to now is just talk about a couple of
到现在为止只是谈论几个
features in jdk 9 that really helped
jdk 9中的功能确实有所帮助
with the migration and i'm picking out
随着迁移，我选择了
to them japchae 38 multi release jar
给他们的japchae 38多功能释放罐
files and Gipp 247 compiled for older
文件和Gipp 247为旧版本编译
platform versions I'll start with multi
平台版本，我将从多
release jar files so Java C 9 has
释放jar文件，以便Java C 9具有
introduced a whole bunch of new API M it
引入了一大堆新的API M
has four handles for example and when
有四个句柄，例如，何时
the wonderful things from far about with
与远处的奇妙事物
var handles is this is you can start
var handles is this is you can start
replacing some of the code that's using
替换正在使用的一些代码
some Muskaan safe to use the standard
一些Muskaan安全使用的标准
api but that creates an interesting
api，但创建一个有趣的
thing and an interesting problem for
事情和一个有趣的问题
those that want to have a library that
那些想要拥有一个图书馆的人
runs on seven or eight and they would
运行七八点，他们会
like to make use of the the new api's
喜欢利用新的API
when they're on nine and so that's going
当他们九点钟的时候
to be interesting how
有趣的是
how do I get that to work another
我如何使它工作
example is the XML catalogue API
示例是XML目录API
standard API introduced in 9 and that
9中引入的标准API
avoids having to hack into the internals
避免不得不侵入内部
of the XML parser code which some
XML解析器代码的一部分
libraries do so this is the motivation
图书馆这样做是出于动机
for multi release and have jar files
用于多版本并具有jar文件
so what multi release jar files do is
所以多版本jar文件的作用是
they extend the jar format to allow
他们扩展了jar格式以允许
multiple Java a specific version class
多个Java特定版本类
files to coexist in the same archive and
文件要共存于同一档案中，并且
I'll show an example of what this of
我将举例说明
this in a second so we start with this
一秒钟，所以我们从这个开始
this is a an example using the jar tool
这是一个使用jar工具的示例
to create a jar file and I'm going to
创建一个jar文件，我要
use the the G RTF to just get the table
使用G RTF来获取表格
of contents this is not new these are
内容不新鲜这些是
this is these are the legacy options
这是这些旧选项
that you can specify to the jar tool for
您可以为jar工具指定
the last 20 years this is how you create
最近20年，这就是您的创造方式
a jar file on the command line this is
命令行上的jar文件是
how you actually get a list of the
您实际上如何获得
contents now let's add some options to
现在让我们向其中添加一些选项
the jar tool because the jar to knows
jar工具，因为要知道的jar
about multi release jars I've added that
关于多释放罐，我已经添加了
when I'm creating the jar file - -
当我创建jar文件时--
release 9 + - c and then i'm giving it a
发行9 +-c，然后我给它一个
completely different directory where i'm
我所在的完全不同的目录
going to find some compiled classes for
会找到一些编译类
jdk 9 and let's look at the contents of
jdk 9，让我们看看
the jar file and see what's happened the
jar文件，看看发生了什么
jar tool has packaged up these classes
jar工具打包了这些类
and is put them into a new section in
并将它们放到
the jar file which is the version
版本的jar文件
section meta-inf such versions slash and
部分meta-inf这样的版本斜杠和
then the version number it's put them
然后是版本号
into versions 9 in this case if you look
在这种情况下，进入第9版
closely you will actually see there are
紧密地，您实际上会看到
two com Acme stats CLI helper class
两个com Acme stats CLI帮助程序类
files in this jar file one in the base
该jar文件中的文件在基础中的一个
section one in the version section so
版本部分中的第一部分
this is interesting I've got classes
这很有趣，我上课了
that that I want to use a nine in this
我想在此使用九
version section
版本部分
now let's suppose I put this jar file on
现在假设我将这个jar文件放在
the classpath with 8 what classes get
具有8个类的类路径
loaded the classes that get loaded are
加载的要加载的类是
from the base section jdk age and older
从jdk年龄段及更高年龄段开始
does not knew about multi release jars
不知道多释放罐
it will never attempt to load classes
它永远不会尝试加载类
from the meta-inf versioned 9 section i
从meta-inf版本9第i部分
put the jar file on the class path with
将jar文件放在类路径上
9 and magically what will happen is the
9神奇的是
class that's in the version section will
版本部分中的类将
override the class in the base section
覆盖基础部分中的类
so this is actually very useful because
所以这实际上非常有用，因为
it means I can ship a library as a multi
这意味着我可以将图书馆作为一个多
release jar and I can have it use one
放罐子，我可以用一个
version of the code when it's on eight
八位时的代码版本
and and and use newer api's that are
和，并使用较新的api
compiled for nine when I'm running on
我在跑步时编译为九
nine so this is actually really really
九点，所以这实际上是真的
useful migration aid however it
有用的移民帮助
introduces complex complexities because
引入复杂的复杂性，因为
I'm now going to have M different source
我现在要有M个不同的来源
different source trees different compile
不同的源树不同的编译
trees and but don't worry about that
树木，但不用担心
there are there are some good recipes
有一些好的食谱
out there and Robert Schulte is talking
在那里，罗伯特·舒尔特（Robert Schulte）在说话
in one of the other rooms in on this
在其他房间之一
topic about maven and integration with
关于Maven和与之集成的主题
JDK 9 I have no idea how they ended up
JDK 9我不知道他们如何结局
putting us scheduled at the same time
让我们在同一时间安排
and but he is going to D is showing an
但是他要去D展示一个
example at this time I'm using maven and
这个时候我正在使用Maven和
some of the recipes he has for creating
他创造的一些食谱
multi release jar files one other thing
多发布jar文件是另一回事
I want to actually want to observe here
我真的想在这里观察
is is that I'm now compiling code for 8
是我现在正在为8编译代码
and then I'm going to be compiling
然后我将要编译
classes that are for 9 does this mean I
9的课程是否表示我
now end up having to J decays in my
现在最终不得不在我的J衰变中
build environment that would be a pain
建立一个痛苦的环境
and this is where the other Jeff comes
这是另一个杰夫来的地方
in 247 compiled older releases count
在247个已编译的较旧版本中计数
comes in because it helps you with this
进来是因为它可以帮助您
problem
问题
we take questions at the end so and
我们最后问问题，所以
historically if you were compiling to an
历史上，如果您要编译到
old release you have to specify three
旧版本，您必须指定三个
options - source
选项-来源
- target - boot class path most people
-目标-引导类路径，大多数人
forget the third one and this is why the
忘记第三个，这就是为什么
Java C compiler has been omitting a
Java C编译器已省略
warning I think since 8:00 on this and
警告，我认为从8:00开始，
because it creates some really
因为它创造了一些真正的
problematic cases with JDK 9 you replace
用您替换的JDK 9有问题的案例
all of this with - - release and then
所有这些都通过--发布，然后
the version you can use JDK 9s Java C to
您可以使用JDK 9s Java C的版本
compile to six seven eight or nine and
编译成六七八八或九
Java C has enough information to know
Java C有足够的信息要知道
what were the public API is in six seven
六个API中的公开API是什么
eight and nine so that it if you've got
八点和九点，如果有的话
some API and you tried to compile it to
一些API，您尝试将其编译为
seven but that API was introduced in
七个，但该API是在
eighth then it'll actually fail the
第八，那么它实际上会失败
compilation so it's a really really
编译，所以它真的是
useful thing to be aware of you combine
意识到你有用的东西
that one multi release jars and you
那一个多放罐子，你
actually have a great solution and a
实际上有一个很好的解决方案，
great combination for a migration one
迁移的绝佳组合
other tool I just want to mention is JD
我只想提及的其他工具是JD
/ scan which is a new tool in JD case in
/ scan这是JD案例中的新工具
J tk9 for doing static analysis like
J tk9用于执行静态分析，例如
Jade EPS and it scans classes for
Jade EPS，它扫描类
deprecated API s and this is becomes
不推荐使用的API，这成为
really really important with deprecation
弃用真的非常重要
for removal because you want to know
删除，因为你想知道
that you're making use of something that
你正在使用的东西
is marked for removal if you see dr
如果您看到博士，则标记为已删除
deprecated are walking around the
弃用的是走来走去
conference he wears a white coat and a
会议上他穿着白大褂，
stethoscope be sure to ask him about GD
听诊器一定要问他关于GD
/ scan and he'll talk to you about that
/扫描，他会和你谈谈
so what can I do to prepare for JDK 9:00
所以我该怎么做才能准备JDK 9:00
a.m. the most important thing is to is
最重要的是
to upgrade the tools and the libraries
升级工具和库
to versions that support JDK 9 in some
某些版本支持JDK 9
cases sadly this might be full stack
不幸的是，这可能是全栈
upgrade especially if you've got older
升级，尤其是如果您年龄较大
versions really old versions of some of
版本真的是某些版本的旧版本
the tools if you only take one thing
工具，如果你只做一件事情
from this session you will need to
在本次会议中，您将需要
upgrade the many many libraries and
升级许多图书馆，
tools and if you do this before you
工具，如果您在执行此操作之前
upgrade to JDK 9 you will save yourself
升级到JDK 9，您将省去很多麻烦
a lot
很多
frustration the modules that are shared
挫败共享的模块
which are the EE that I listed out
我列出的EE
earlier in the presentation is
在演讲的前面是
properties really really problematic for
属性确实对
those that depend on those those modules
那些依赖那些模块的
there are several migration options and
有几个迁移选项，
you can figure out what way you want to
你可以找出想要的方式
go the Jade EPS tool is really really
真正使用Jade EPS工具
useful to have and be able to analyze
有用并且能够分析
your code to see whether it's using any
您的代码以查看是否正在使用任何
any any internal api's try out JDK 9
任何内部api的JDK 9试用
look for the legal reflective access
寻找合法的反射访问
warnings and submit bugs that's the
警告并提交错误
important thing so that the code that is
重要的是，这样的代码是
doing these naughty things can can be
做这些淘气的事情可以是
addressed by those that maintain that
那些坚持认为
code if you parse the class void these
代码，如果您解析类使这些无效
are the the version Java version and
是Java版本，
property please revisit that code
物业，请重新访问该代码
because the possibilities is high that
因为可能性很高
it may not work in 9 and read the
它可能无法在9中使用并阅读
release notes nobody reads the release
发行说明没有人阅读发行
notes JDK 9 has has 43 pages of release
注释JDK 9具有43页的发行版
notes which is probably any problem that
注意这可能是任何问题
you learn into can actually you will
你学习可以实际上你会
actually find a release note would
实际找到发行说明会
actually will detail that it does
实际上会详细说明
there's an extreme amount of detail in
里面有很多细节
there for the map vast majority of that
那里的地图绝大多数
detail and and the issues in those
细节和那些问题
release notes is at the same level of
发行说明与
the release notes and the same level of
发行说明和相同级别的
changes that you will see in in 7 &amp; 8
您将在7和8中看到的更改
how do you prepare for post JDK 9 why am
您如何为发布JDK 9做准备，为什么
I talking about post JDK 9 this week
我本周谈论的是JDK 9发布
you'll be hearing about the proposed in
您将听到有关提议的
a new release model where there's a
一个新的发行模型，其中有一个
major release or being a smaller than
主要版本或小于
what we've done before every six months
我们每六个月所做的工作
and this means that things are going to
这意味着事情将会
move faster we hope and it means that we
我们希望移动得更快，这意味着我们
will have an opportunity to finally work
将有机会最后工作
through the eventual steps on removing
通过有关删除的最终步骤
the the modules shared with Java EE so
与Java EE共享的模块
that means you will need to figure out
这意味着您需要弄清楚
your how you going to migrate to the
您将如何迁移到
standalone versions again run Jade EPS
独立版本再次运行Jade EPS
really really important there isn't a
真的非常重要，没有
proposed plan yet how we will eventually
拟议的计划，但我们最终将如何
encapsulate the api's at runtime the
在运行时封装api
warning and allowing code and the class
警告并允许代码和类
path to continue to hack will
继续黑客的道路将
will is what you have a nine but
将是你有一个九，但
eventually we want to get to the point
最终我们要讲到重点
where the internals are completely
内部结构完全
encapsulated running with illegal access
封装运行非法访问
oh I see a type of air that should be
哦，我看到一种应该是的空气
I ll L of course and illegal access
我当然会和非法访问
equal deny allows you to test out future
平等否认可以让您测试未来
behavior now because it will deny access
现在就行动，因为它会拒绝访问
it means a code that tries to do naughty
这意味着试图调皮的代码
things will get the right and illegal
事情会变得正确和违法
access error illegal act exceptionally
访问错误非法行为
are inaccessible object exceptions again
再次成为不可访问的对象异常
audits your code for the version string
审核您的代码以获取版本字符串
especially if the version string changes
特别是如果版本字符串更改
again and test the EA bills I think this
再次测试EA帐单，我认为这
is actually we found this the most
实际上我们发现这个最多
useful thing with nine the EA bills
有用的九个EA账单
early access bills were available right
可以使用早期访问账单吧
from the start every build was actually
从一开始，每个构建实际上都是
published and that allowed cloud
发布，并允许云
libraries and maintainer to actually
库和维护者实际上
work with us from the start and deal
从一开始就与我们合作并达成协议
deal with issues so summary most code
处理问题，所以总结大多数代码
will work online without changes I've
可以在线工作而无需更改
talked about very few changes that
谈到很少的变化
actually require code except for the
实际上需要代码，除了
partly cloudy and the Java version JDK
部分多云，Java版本为JDK
nine does include some disruptive
九个确实包括一些破坏性的
changes I think I've covered most of
我认为我涵盖了大多数变化
those changes and again make sure you
这些更改，并再次确保您
upgrade your tools and libraries in
升级您的工具和库
advance to avoid most of the issues
提前避免大多数问题
that's the most important message from
这是最重要的信息
this presentation so more information
此演示文稿，以便更多信息
and JDK 9 has a an open JDK has a
JDK 9有一个开放的JDK有一个
project JDK 9 and you will see all the
项目JDK 9，您将看到所有
chips that I showed at the beginning of
我在开始时展示的筹码
this presentation
这个演讲
those chips are full of really really
这些筹码真的充满了
useful information if you have the time
有空的话有用的信息
to read it there's a migration guide
要阅读它，有一个迁移指南
which is actually not too bad that
其实还不错
covers most of the main issues that you
涵盖了您的大部分主要问题
potentially will run into there's lots
可能会碰到很多
of sessions about JDK 9 this week is so
关于JDK 9的会议本周是如此
and try to attend those if you can now
并尝试参加那些，如果你现在可以的话
just a reminder of our sessions so
只是提醒我们的会议
myself
我
Alex Buckley Mark Reinhold we have 5
亚历克斯·巴克利·马克·莱因霍尔德我们有5
sessions in this room and Alex is doing
会议在这个房间里，而亚历克斯正在做
module development with JDK 9 here and
在这里使用JDK 9开发模块
at 5:30 this evening mark is doing
今天晚上5:30在做
modules in one lesson and migrating to
一课中的模块并迁移到
modules in this room tomorrow at 11:30
明天11:30在这个房间里的模块
and 150
和150
and then Alex is back on Wednesday at
然后亚历克斯在星期三回到
9:30 to do modules and services and so
9：30做模块和服务等等
that's that that's the the the sessions
那就是那届会议
that I want to plug because it's we're
我想插入，因为这是我们
trapped within a track essentially stay
被困在一条轨道上基本上停留
connected and there's a DevOps corner
连接并且有一个DevOps角落
and that folks here that are working on
那些在这里工作的人
the JDK will be around around over the
JDK将在
next few days and some links and there
接下来的几天以及一些链接
as well and don't believe anything I
也不要相信我
said please don't buy anything based on
说请不要购买任何基于
anything I said and so that's it so
我说的任何话就是这样
let's see we have a minute or two for
让我们看看我们有一两分钟的时间
questions and I don't know whether
问题，我不知道是否
there's no microphone here so I will
这里没有麦克风，所以我会
have to repeat your your question if so
如果是这样，必须重复您的问题
that it's because we're actually being
那是因为我们实际上是
recorded here okay so the question is is
记录在这里好吧，所以问题是
for this jar file what happens when I'm
对于这个jar文件，当我
on ten and so in this or 18.3 okay so in
在十点左右，或者在18.3点这样
this case is this is assuming there
这种情况是假设
isn't a a section that has four for ten
不是一个十个有四个的部分
or 18.3 then it'll just go to the
或18.3，它将直接转到
previous version which is nine so this
以前的版本是九个，所以这个
case it would it would load the main
它将加载主
class from the base section and it would
基础部分的课程，它将
load the helper class from the version
从版本加载帮助程序类
section
部分
I'm sorry I didn't quite you Tom about
对不起，汤姆，我不是很了解你
the size of the jar file okay so the I
jar文件的大小还可以，所以我
think the question is is just as the jar
认为问题就像罐子一样
file get larger with these additional
这些额外的文件变得更大
classes and yeah yes it would be because
类，是的，那是因为
it's sizes jar files proportional to
它与jar文件的大小成正比
that to the number of entries in it okay
到它的条目数还可以
so the question is is for this example
所以问题是这个例子
why is the the main class and not in the
为什么是主要阶级而不是
inversion section so for this particular
反转部分，因此对于此特定
example the the main class does not have
例如主类没有
any JDK 9 specific code it's only this
任何JDK 9特定代码，仅此而已
helper class that that is used for this
用于此的帮助程序类
example I did the helper class has the
例如我做的辅助类有
nine specific code so there's two
九个特定的代码，所以有两个
versions of the helper class right
助手类的版本权利
exactly someone that someone actually
确实是某人
just went out is a bit like overlays and
刚出去有点像覆盖和
patching okay so the the question is is
修补好，所以问题是
as I mentioned some incompatibility with
正如我提到的与
and the e modules so there's there's an
和e模块，所以有一个
one you want me to expand on that this
一个你想让我扩展这一点
is a couple of areas one is the
是几个领域之一是
transaction API that's really really
真正的交易API
problematic Java C you'll need to find a
有问题的Java C，您需要找到一个
small subset of the transaction API if
交易API的一小部分，如果
you look in the Javik transaction and
你看Javik交易，
package within java c you'll only see
Java C中的软件包，您只会看到
three exceptions in there that's the
那里的三个例外
minimal that's actually required by the
实际需要的最小数量
java ideal and spec to support the
Java的理想和规格，以支持
mapping of CORBA transaction exceptions
CORBA事务异常的映射
to remote exceptions and another
远程异常和另一个
problematic area is the so-called common
问题区域是所谓的共同点
annotations where Java C defines is the
Java C定义的注释是
smallest subset of those annotations to
这些注释的最小子集
support web services so they're really
支持网络服务，因此它们确实
really problematic areas and so they
确实有问题的地区，所以他们
they will be the two main problem areas
他们将是两个主要问题领域
okay so I think that the question is is
好吧，我认为问题是
is is about crypto providers right so
是关于加密货币提供商的，所以
they should do it so um crypto for
他们应该这样做，所以加密
providers if they're deployed should
提供者（如果已部署）应该
work as before yes in it in addition the
像以前一样在其中工作
jce has been updated to be able to
jce已更新，能够
support deploying crypto providers as
支持将加密提供商部署为
modules as well okay any other questions
模块以及其他任何问题
okay I think we're we're done okay thank
好吧，我想我们已经完成了，谢谢
you for attending
你参加
[Applause]
[掌声]